# VITALIY KOLOMIETS

JUNIOR FRONT END DEVEPOLER

## **INFO**

#### **ADDRESS**

Odessa, 65123, Ukraine

#### **PHONE**

+38(067) 291-77-11

#### **EMAIL**

kolumb.vk@gmail.com

## **LINKS**

#### **FACEBOOK**

https://www.facebook.com/kolomietsvitaliy

#### **LINKEDIN**

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kolomiets-vitaliy/

#### **GITHUB**

https://github.com/vertalik

#### **INSTAGRAM**

https://www.instagram.com/kolomiets.vitaliy\_87/

#### **TELEGRAM**

https://t.me/kolomiets\_vitaliy

## **PORTFOLIO**

https://vertalik.github.io/

## **SKILLS**

HTML5

CSS3

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$ 

**JAVASCRIPT** 

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$ 

LESS / SASS

**BOOTSTRAP 4** 

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

**GITHUB** 

 $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\bullet$   $\circ$   $\circ$ 

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$ 

• • 0 0 0

# LANGUAGES

**RUSSIAN** 

UKRAINIAN

**ENGLISH** 

. . . . .

## **PROFILE**

I am keen on computer engineering.

When I was working as a software engineer at M-service (mobile phone repair company) I wrote a soft by Delphi which helped me to do my work faster.

I have been self-employed in retail since 2015.

I have written a storehouse soft by 1C.

I was improving my programming skills and I realized why I want my job to be connected with web development.

Odessa

Odessa

Odessa

Odessa

Odessa

Odessa

Odessa

Odessa

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Software engineer at M-service (Mobile phone repair)

Aug 2010 - Jun 2015

Retail, Self-employed

Jul 2015 - Present

# **EDUCATION**

## **Computer engineering at Odessa Technical College**

Sep 2004 - Jan 2009

Computer systems and networks at Odessa National **Polytechnic University** 

Sep 2009 - Jun 2010

## **COURSES**

## Front End Basic at Hillel IT School

Aug 2019 - Oct 2019

Certificate: https://github.com/vertalik/vertalik.github.io/blob/master/Certificate/FE\_basic.png

Front End Pro at Hillel IT School

Dec 2019 - Apr 2020

Certificate: https://github.com/vertalik/vertalik.github.io/blob/master/Certificate/FE\_pro.png

**Englsih Elementary at Green Forest English School** 

Jul 2019 - Sep 2019

**Englsih Pre-intermediate at Green Forest English School** 

Sep 2019 - Nov 2019